YYeTs人人影视字幕组出品
更多原创字幕翻译 请登陆www.YYeTs.com
时间轴：YY 孤帆字幕总监： YY
翻译： 小赛喵  非燕  阿蘅  猫中之王 孤帆  字幕总监： YY
校对： YY    后期：孤帆 字幕总监： YY
老爸老妈浪漫史
第七季  第十九集
孩子们  2012年的春天
Kids, in the spring of 2012,
你们巴尼叔叔突然失联了好几周
your Uncle Barney went off the grid for a couple weeks.
所以等他发短信让我去他家时
So I was relieved when I got a text
我松了一口气
asking me to come over to his place.
很高兴收到你短信  兄弟
Glad to hear from you, buddy.
我还挺担心你是不是遭遇...
I was worried something bad happened...
不测了
...to you.
欢迎你  我的兄弟
Welcome, brother.
这是干嘛
What is this?
泰德·艾弗琳·莫斯比
Ted Evelyn Mosby,
你将宣誓替我守密
you are about to be sworn to secrecy
要以神圣兄弟的誓言起誓
through the sacred vows of a Bro Oath,
或简称"兄言"
or "Broath."
请穿上你的"兄袍"
Please, put on your "Brobe."
我才不要穿这破"兄袍"
Yeah, I'm not putting on the "Brobe."
泰德  你就...
Ted, just...
配合点  可以吗
just... Okay?
* 兄...*
* Broooo... *
等等  这格列高利圣咏是在吟唱"兄"字吗
Wait, are they chanting "Bro"?"?
格列高利圣咏  是罗马天主教做弥撒时所用的音乐
* 兄... *
* Bro... *
我找了些当地的僧人给我录的
I got some local monks to record this.
没错  我佛教界也有人
Yeah! I got a monk guy.
厉害吧
Cool, right?
是蛮厉害的
It actually is, yeah.
我刻张碟给你
I'll burn it for you.
"兄言"仪式结束后提醒我就行
Just remind me after The Broath.
言归正传  泰德·艾弗琳·莫斯比
Anyway, Ted Evelyn Mosby,
宣誓仪式后  你就要永远为我保守秘密
this ritual forever binds you to keep a solemn secret...
什么秘密
Which is?
我真的好喜欢昆茵哦
I really like this Quinn girl!
我们最近总是形影不离
We've been spending tons of time together,
我好想带她见见大伙
and I want the gang to meet her.
不过我又怕其他人会反对  原因...
but I'm afraid they're gonna disapprove because,
你懂的
well, you know.
我确实懂
I did know. You see,
昆茵是个脱衣舞娘
Quinn was a stripper...
还坑过巴尼不少钱
who had swindled Barney out of quite a bit of cash.
我们打算请大伙来昆茵家吃饭
We're inviting everyone to dinner at Quinn's,
我不想大家对她有成见
and I want them to keep an open mind,
所以才需要你以"兄言"的名义起誓
which brings us to The Broath.
把你的手放在《兄弟法典》上
Place your hand on The Bro Code.
好  好  随便
Yeah, yeah, yeah...
随我复诵
Repeat after me.
我  泰德·"艾弗琳"·莫斯比
I, Ted Evelyn Mosby...
我  泰德·"跟你说我中间名真蠢"·莫斯比
"I, Ted "Why Did I Ever Tell You My Middle Name" Mosby..."
慎重地起誓  不会给大伙们泄露半句
...solemnly swear not to tell our friends
昆茵是个脱衣舞娘的事
that Quinn is a stripper.
慎重地起誓  不会给大伙们泄露半句
"...solemnly swear not to tell our friends
昆茵是个脱衣舞娘  还坑了你不少钱的事
that Quinn is a stripper" Who duped you out of lots of money.
你复诵我说的就行了
You're only supposed to repeat after me.
"You're only supposed to repeat after me."
-别闹了  -别闹了
- Stop it. - Stop it.
肃静
Silence!
我知道我和昆茵一开始不是很顺遂
Look, I know that things started out sketchy with me and Quinn,
但我真的很喜欢她  就行行好吧
but I really like her, so please.
你
Do you,
泰德·中名省略·莫斯比
Ted Middle-Name-Omitted Mosby,
愿意发誓永远遵守"兄言"吗
swear to uphold this Broath?
我愿意
I do.
巴尼跟一个会把他钱骗光光的脱衣舞娘好上了
Barney's dating a stripper who's gonna steal all his money!
好了  该昆茵家吃饭啦  记住
Okay, time to go to Quinn's. Now remember,
我什么都没说过  知道吗
I told you nothing, okay?
巴尼真的很希望我们都喜欢她
Barney really wants us all to like her.
怎么可能呀
But how can we?
巴尼被人玩弄于股掌之间  还浑然不觉
Quinn totally duped Barney, and he couldn't even see it.
显然  昆茵的床技让巴尼忘却了一切
Well, apparently, the sex is mind-blowing.
我也有过这种经历  没错
Ha, I've been there. Yeah.
某个妞开门时
I was once with this chick who answered the door
上身赤裸  涂满奶油  脖戴狗链
wearing nothing but, uh, whipped cream, a dog collar
粉红丁字绕股沟
and a hot pink thong.
马修  你不能用"某个妞"来说你的性事
Marshall, you can't tell sex stories about "This chick,"
因为大家都知道那个妞是我
because everyone knows it's me.
你这辈子只跟我一个女人爽过
I'm the only woman you've ever been with.
这不公平  他们都能显摆跟妞的性事
It's not fair, the guys are always telling their sex stories
我有更好的却不能说
and I can top every one of them.
宝贝  二十个性感风骚妞才荟萃成一个风情万种的你
Baby, you're like 20 slutty chicks all rolled into one.
说再多的甜言蜜语也没用
Sweet talk is not going to change my mind.
别再岔题
Let's focus.
今晚  我们得看清
Tonight, we want to make sure
昆茵到底是不是在骗巴尼的钱
that Quinn is not out to scam Barney.
所以  当三个小时后重回这里时
So, when we walk back through that door three hours from now,
我们心中都得有个答案
we should all be able to answer one simple question:
三小时后
这女人我们信不信得过
Do we trust this girl?
先提一点
Well, for one thing,
她控制欲有点儿强
she seems kind of controlling.
要端鹰嘴豆泥出来吗  兔兔宝贝
Is it okay if I put out the hummus, bunny face?
不许  留着当甜点
No, save it for dessert.
白痴
Idiot.
再来点红酒吗  天鹅美妞
More red wine, beauty-swan?
她酒量超好
She drinks a lot.
-我可以去尿尿吗  甜心小绵羊  -不准
- Is it okay if I go pee, sugar lamb? - No!
你不是三个小时前刚去尿过吗
You just went three hours ago.
你说得对  熊宝宝
You're right, baby bear!
那又如何  就算巴尼是妻管严
Yes, so Barney's whipped;
也不代表昆茵就是个骗子啊
it doesn't mean that Quinn is a con artist.
要不是因为某两个人一直在岔题
Well, maybe we could've gotten a better read on her
或许我们会更多机会分析她了
if two people hadn't gone off topic.
顺带一提  昆茵  你这公寓真不错
By the way, Quinn, your apartment is amazing.
是啊  真漂亮
Oh, yeah, it's beautiful.
其实我快要搬了
I'm actually moving out soon.
你们有认识人想租房吗
If you know anyone looking for a sublet,
这里有租金管制制度
this place is rent-controlled.
价钱划算到让你们难以置信
You would not believe what I pay.
孩子们  那段时间
Kids, things have been tense
我和罗宾的关系变得紧张
between Robin and I for weeks.
她搬走后
Ever since she moved out,
我把公寓让给了马修和莉莉
and I gave the apartment to Marshall and Lily,
然后自己跑去住大学宿舍
I'd been crashing in university housing.
都晚上十点了  我靠
It's 10 o'clock, damn it.
耐德  马丁和米莉
Ned, Martin and Millie,
有人想好好睡觉呢
people are trying to sleep!
你年轻时不也这样吗
Hey, you were young like us once, right?
我年轻时  才不是你们这样
I was never like you guys.
罗宾则是去她同事帕拉里斯家住
And Robin was staying with her coworker, Patrice.
你今天心情好像不太好啊  罗宾
You seem so down today, Robin.
我烤了点饼干哦
I made you cookies.
我靠  帕拉里斯  你想烦死我呀
Damn it, Patrice, stop smothering me!
因此  当昆茵说出她的公寓待租的时候...
So, when Quinn said her apartment was available...
我的  我的  我的
It's mine! It's mine! It's mine!
我先  我先  我先
Dibs! Dibs! Dibs!
岔题的是我们吗  那马修算什么
We got off topic? What about Marshall?
我只是附和那个
Hey, I was just going along with
提议要玩游戏的人而已
whoever suggested we play that game.
大伙们  来玩个游戏吧
Hey, let's play a game!
来说说"公共场合最刺激的性爱经历"  我先说
Uh, craziest sex-in-public story; I'll start.
曾经有某个妞
I was once with this chick
她爱在电梯里"性"奋
who loved to get freaky in elevators.
门一关上  她会突然间
Doors would close; suddenly,
四脚着地喘粗气  像只发情的母狗
she's panting on all fours like a dog in heat.
马修  别说了
Marshall, stop.
我可没说过那人就是你
I never said that it was you.
好吧  不管怎样  去年八月
Okay, so anyway, last August,
我和这个小荡妇做爱时没戴套
I go bareback with this same slut.
结果她怀孕了  此后这妞性欲更强了
She get's pregnant; bitch is even hornier.
是吗  我也和某个男的交往过
Oh, yeah? I was once with this dude
被我发现他在做爱时吃三明治
who I caught eating a sandwich during sex.
大肉丸掉出来  砸过我背上
Big ol' meatball falls out, lands on my back,
一直滚到电梯地板上
rolls on to the elevator floor.
恶心吧
Hmm. Disgusting, right?
怎么了  我可没说那人就是你
What, I never said it was you.
是啊  抱歉我们没你们那么专注
Yeah, sorry we didn't stay as laser-focused as you guys.
至少我发现了些证据
Hey, at least I got some evidence.
瞧我在昆茵卧室里发现了什么
Look what I found in Quinn's bedroom.
巴尼要带她去夏威夷
Barney's taking her to Hawaii.
莉莉  你还偷翻她的东西了
Lily, you snooped through her stuff?
才没有  我不过是用开信刀
No. It's like the first thing you see
偷偷打开她的抽屉  一眼就看到了
when you Jimmy open her desk drawer with a letter opener
她日记里面还说  这开信刀是她奶奶留给她的呢
her grandfather left her, according to her diary.
一等舱机票
First-class tickets,
四星级酒店  这得花巴尼不少钱呢
a four-star hotel-- this cost Barney a fortune.
对  这证明昆茵只是把巴尼当金主
Yeah, this proves that Quinn is totally using him for his money.
好了  莉莉  别闹了
You know what, Lily, enough.
伙计们  即使你们说得没错  但这是巴尼的事
Guys, even if you're right about Quinn, this is Barney.
他迟早会意识到的
He'll come to his senses.
我们再等一周  最多两周
I give this whole thing a week, two weeks, tops.
现在  我们有事要宣布
And now, we have an announcement.
能让我来说吗
Can I tell them?
不行
No.
-我们要同居了  -我们...
- We're moving in together - We're m...
-恭喜  太好了  -真替你们高兴
- Congrats! That's great. - So happy for you.
我们得棒打鸳鸯了
We gotta end this.
对
Yup.
孩子们  你们应该记得
Kids, as you'll recall,
我们这伙人会通过隐晦的方式
our gang had a subtle way of letting someone know
让朋友知道他们在犯错
they were making a mistake.
劝诫大会
你去哪里了
Where have you been?
没白跑  等等
Oh, worth it. Hang on.
戒茵大会
我们事后肯定会恨死自己的  对吧
You know we would've hated ourselves, right?
所以
So,
罗宾有说今天自己偷摸着干嘛了吗
did Robin tell you the incredibly devious thing she did today?
怎么是我
Me?!
我刚碰巧来这个小区
Hey, so I just happened to be in the neighborhood
然后灵光一闪  "天啊  昆茵身材那么好"
and I thought, "Man, Quinn is in such great shape,
"她一定喜欢吃水果"
she must love fruit."
对了  随便问下
So, unrelated,
你代租人找得怎么样了
how's the search for a sub-letter going?
这也太巧了吧
This is such a weird coincidence!
罗宾也"正好碰巧"来这个小区
Robin also "just happened" to be in the neighborhood
还带了一瓶酒和她的信用评级
with a bottle of wine and her credit scores.
你俩真是不可理喻
I can't believe you two.
你们更在意什么
What do you care about more,
是保护朋友不受伤害
protecting your friend from getting hurt
还是抢占这个姑娘的公寓
or scoring this girl's apartment?
那房子有个能用的壁炉
There's a working fireplace!
帕拉里斯把我的裤子都给烫坏了
Patrice is ironing my pants all wrong!
你们真该感到难为情
You guys should be ashamed.
说到难为情
Speaking of shame,
以前有某个妞  她喜欢在麦凯伦酒吧
I was once with this chick who liked to do hand stuff
我们最喜欢的小隔间里
underneath a jacket while we were all
盖着外套帮我打手枪
sitting around our favorite booth at MacLaren's.
真恶心
Gross.
我们前菜可是一起吃的
We share appetizers.
好吧  我以前交往过的某个男的
Okay, well, I was once with a dude
连意淫下三人行都不敢
who couldn't even fantasize about a three-way.
他就只会说  "她可是你的闺蜜"
He was all, "Ew, she's your best friend."
干嘛现在说
What now?
我以前交往过的某个妞
I was once with a chick who wanted
想在演学校话剧《彼得潘》的时候亲热
to get it on during a school production of Peter Pan.
我...等等  你说的不是我
Well, I... Wait, that wasn't me.
还是继续聊帕拉里斯和烫衣服的事吧
So, back to Patrice and this ironing issue...
我以为你所有的第一次都是和我做的
I thought I was the first girl you ever did anything with.
所有认真的第一次
Anything serious.
别告诉我你嫉妒我在十年级时
Please don't tell me that you're jealous of me getting
和珍娜·克里斯托莉进行到二垒[摸胸]
to second base in tenth grade with Jenna Cristalli.
别当着我们宝宝的面提那个婊子的名字
Don't say that whore's name in front of our baby.
什么事
What's going on?
巴尼  这是场劝说大会
Barney, this in an intervention.
是"戒茵大会"
A "Quinntervention."
你和奎茵进展太快了  而我们不信任她
You and Quinn are moving really fast, and we don't trust her.
我们只是让你留个心眼
We're just looking out for your best interests.
"留心昆茵"
"Quinn-terests."
我不明白
I don't understand. Wh...
等等
Wait a sec.
泰德·艾弗琳·莫斯比
Ted Evelyn Mosby...
你违反了"兄言"
you broke The Broath.
你可别血口喷人
How dare you?!
"兄言"是兄弟间最神圣的...
A Broath is the most sacred bond between--
是  我违反了
okay, yeah, I did.
你知道违反"兄言"后果严重
Are you aware that breaking a Broath can have deadly,
甚至可能招来杀生之祸吗
even fatal repercussions?
-你有学过历史吗  泰德  -我古今皆通
- Have you studied history, Ted? - Extensively.
可我对捏造的历史一窍不通  所以...
But I'm a little shaky on fake history, so...
违反"兄言"的惨痛代价
The tragic cost of a broken Broath
可以追溯到古"罗兄"时期
dates back to Ancient Bro-man times...
兄鲁图
Hey, Bro-tus,
源自罗马政治家布鲁图[Brutus]
马尔库斯·尤尼乌斯·布鲁图是凯撒最宠爱的助手、挚友和养子
要是有一群人合谋刺杀我
you'd tell me if, like, a bunch of dudes
你会告诉我的  对吧
were conspiring to assassinate me, right?
没错  凯撒
Um, totally, Caesar.
被害妄想症又烦了吧
Paranoid much?
我只是想确定
Just to be sure,
你能对着"兄言"发誓吗
can you swear a Broath to me?
好  我发誓
Sure. I swear.
谢了
Thanks.
就知道你一直都挺我
You've always got my back.
[恺撒被一班反对君主制的罗马元老院成员一人一刀捅死
行刺者包括布鲁图]
你也有份吗  兄鲁图
Et tu, Bro-te?
"Et tu, brute"出自英国文艺复兴时期
大文豪威廉·莎士比亚的作品《儒略·恺撒》
然后他上了上百个妞
And then he banged, like, a hundred chicks
还发明了凯撒沙拉
and invented a salad.
凯撒沙拉则是由一名墨西哥餐厅主厨
凯撒·卡迪尼在1924年发明
真事哟
True story.
昆茵骗了你  还把你玩弄于股掌之间
Well, Quinn lied to you, she manipulated you.
如果她只是在利用你呢
What if she's just using you?
她没有利用我
She's not just using me.
夏威夷奢华之旅怎么说呢
What about the expensive trip to Hawaii?
什么夏威夷奢华之旅
What expensive trip to Hawaii?
那是我为你准备的
The one I got for you.
那本来是给巴尼的惊喜
That was supposed to be a surprise for Barney.
巴尼让我来这里找他
He asked me to meet him here.
你们在做什么
What's going on, you guys?
告诉她
Tell her.
好  那我来告诉她[我来塞满她]
Fine, I'll fill her in.
我现在一肚子火
And I am so angry,
都没心情开黄色玩笑了
I'm not even gonna make a joke about "filling her in."
虽然我昨晚塞了三次  自己鼓掌
Which I did three times last night, self-five.
我朋友觉得你不适合我
My friends think you're wrong for me,
所以他们在开劝诫大会
so they're having an intervention.
是"戒茵大会"
A "Quinntervention."
我不明白
I don't understand.
你叫昆茵嘛  "戒"是指...
Well, see, your name is Quinn, and so...
我来解释
I'll explain.
我让泰德不要告诉他们你的职业
I made Ted promise not to tell them what you do,
但是他还是说了
but he did,
现在他们不信任你
and now they don't trust you.
还真是伤人啊
Wow, that really hurts.
但让我更伤心的是
But what's even worse is that
你居然觉得有必要隐瞒我的职业
you felt the need to lie about me.
巴尼  我不已自己为耻
I'm not ashamed of who I am, Barney,
但你却觉得不光彩
but you clearly are.
我没有觉得不光彩
I'm not ashamed of you.
我只是不想让他们对你妄下评判
I just didn't want them to judge you without...
也许我们是进展得太快了
Maybe we are moving too fast.
什么  你这话什么意思
What? What is that supposed to mean?
我没办法继续了
I don't think I can do this.
你就这样和我分手吗
Wait, are you ending things just like that?
如果你走出那扇门  就证明他们是对的
If you walk out that door, you prove them right.
也证明了  你是个绝情寡义的脱衣舞娘
You prove that you're just some heartless stripper
一心在乎的是我的钱而不是...
who never gave a damn about me in the...
别找我了
Don't call me.
真是紧张又激烈
Wow. That was intense.
我们刚刚破坏了
We just destroyed what could have been
一个千载难逢的幸福机会
a once-in-a-lifetime shot at happiness.
我知道  我也很自责
I know. I feel guilty, too.
壁炉  阳台
Fireplace, balcony,
硬木地板
hardwood floors...
够了  我就直说吧
Okay, I'll just say it:
在我们发生那么多事后
After everything that happened between us,
我真不敢相信你居然还不肯放手
I can't believe you wouldn't back down
把昆茵的房子让给我
and let me have Quinn's place.
泰德  我们能出去聊聊吗
Ted, can I talk to you out in the hall?
你有没有想过
Has it ever occurred to you
过去的几周  我也很难熬
that the last few weeks haven't been easy for me either?
一天之内  我感情破裂
In the span of one day, my engagement fell apart,
痛失挚友  无家可归
I lost my best friend, then I lost my apartment.
而现在  我又即将变成无业游民
And-and now I'm about to lose my job.
这话什么意思
What do you mean?
我最近无法专心工作
I-I've been completely distracted at work.
老板要我周五五点去见他
And now my boss wants to see me Friday at 5:00,
全办公室的人都知道那是"炒鱿鱼专点"
which, around the office, is known as "fire o'clock."
我不知道
I had no idea.
你怎么可能知道
How could you?
我唯一想与之倾诉的那个人
The one person I want to talk to most barely looks me
现在不愿看我一眼  更别说回我电话了
in the eye anymore, much less returns my calls.
泰德  我知道向我表白需要很大的勇气
Ted, I know it took guts to tell me you love me.
我也知道我没有接受你有多伤心
And I-I know how much it hurt that I didn't say it back,
但是...
but...
该死的  我心里也不好受
Damn it, th-this sucks for me,  too.
我想你
And I-I miss you.
我们能不能...
Is there any way we can just...
重新做回朋友
go back to normal?
我们回不去了
I don't think I can do normal anymore.
巴尼还是没回电话
Barney still isn't answering.
我们得找到他  向他道歉
We gotta go find him and apologize.
我还以为是昆茵呢
Oh. I thought you were Quinn.
巴尼  真的很抱歉
Barney, we're so sorry.
我们不该这么蛮横插手你的事
We never should've meddled like that.
-你能原谅我们吗  -我不知道
- Can you forgive us? - I don't know.
你们没有权利那么做
You had no right to do that.
兄弟  那你想我们怎么补偿你
How can we make it up to you, buddy?
我  巴尼的死党之一
I, one of Barney's best friends...
"I, one of Barney's best friends..."
发誓再也不会干涉他的私人生活
...promise never to interfere with his personal life again...
"...promise never to interfere with his personal life again..."
除非涉及到身体健康  国家安全
...unless it's an issue of health, national security,
或他准备上一个胖妞
or he's about to get up on a fattie.
除非涉及到身体健康  国家安全
"...unless it's an issue of health, national security,
或他准备上一个胖妞
or he's about to get up on a fattie."
现在  两位女士请亲吻对方
And now, to seal this sacred vow,
-以吻封住这庄严的誓言  -巴尼
- the two ladies will kiss. - Barney...
两位女士请亲吻对方
The two ladies will kiss!
莉莉
Lil...
好了
Okay.
现在该男士了
And now the gentlemen.
老兄
Dude...
现在该男士了
And now the gentlemen!
-我们就...  -太乱来了
- Let's just... - This is silly.
别  别碰我的脸
Don't-don't touch my face.
我本来要说
I was going to say,
"现在该男士碰拳封住誓言"
"And now the gentlemen bump fists."
你们俩想亲对方多久了呀
How long you been holding back that one?
太香艳了  老兄
Hot stuff, fellas.
是有伸舌头吗
Did I see a little tongue in there?
这是怎么回事
I don't understand.
如果这两位不是那么如胶似漆的话
Well, if these two will keep their sweaty paws off each other
我就解释给你们听
for half a second, I'll explain.
这是因为几天前...
It all started a couple days ago...
我想带你去见我的朋友
I want you to meet my friends.
我应该紧张吗
Should I be nervous?
就像你带我回家见家长一样
Is it like bringing me home to meet your parents?
不  不  不
No, no, no.
比见家长更有压力
Much more stressful than that.
我的朋友们虽然很棒  但又自以为是
You see, my friends, while awesome, can be presumptuous,
爱管闲事  搞砸事情功夫一流
meddlesome and downright destructive.
当他们知道你的职业  知道我们如何邂逅
When they learn what you do and how we met,
他们很可能会想办法拆散我们
they'll probably try to break us up.
不如我们就将计就计
So let's have some fun with them.
陪他们玩玩
Mess with their heads.
你是说  整人计划吗
Are you saying... evil plan?
正是此意
Hells to the yes.
天啊  你真撩人
My God, you're hot.
等等
Wait for it.
我们的计划如下
Here's what we do.
我会让泰德发誓不向任何人透露有关你的事
I'll make Ted swear not to tell anyone what he knows about you,
他肯定会立马跑去泄密
and he'll cave immediately.
巴尼跟一个会把他钱骗光光的脱衣舞娘好上了
Barney's dating a stripper who's gonna steal all his money!
接着  我们邀请大伙来做客
Next, we invite everyone over.
我会不断征求你的意见
I'll keep saying stuff like:
要端鹰嘴豆泥出来吗  兔兔宝贝
Is it okay if I put out the hummus, bunny face?
我则摆出悍妇的样子来回答
And I'll be the bossy bitch who says:
不许  留着当甜点  白痴
No, save it for dessert, idiot.
太棒了
Nice.
最后  我们会宣布
And, finally, we'll announce...
我们俩要同居了
We're moving in together!
我有个主意
I've got an idea.
让你的朋友泰德和罗宾
Let's get your friends Ted and Robin
一起争夺我的公寓吧
fighting over my apartment.
等等   这对于咱俩有啥好处吗
Wait, what does that have to do with you and me?
没好处  我就爱损人不利己
Nothing. I just worship chaos.
你真是让我欲火焚身
I can't handle how hot you are right now.
-再等等  -接下来
- Wait for it. - Next,
他们会劝我和你分手
they'll try to talk me into dumping you.
我则正好撞见此事
And I'll walk in on it.
然后我们假装分手
Then we pretend to break up.
当他们回来
And when they crawl back,
跪求我的原谅时
begging for forgiveness...
我就装出大人有大量的样子  原谅他们
I'll be the bigger man and let them off the hook.
又或者  将他们玩弄于股掌之间
Or make the monkeys dance for you.
我的天啊  你太有才了
God, you're smart!
这将会成为传
It's gonna be legen...
我再也等不了了
I'm not waiting for it anymore.
奇
...dary.
我的天啊  你们俩真是
My God, you two are...
天造地设的一对
Perfect together.
所以你不打算搬进来了吗
So you're not really moving in?
一开始我们只是开玩笑而已
Well, it started out as a joke,
可当我们越深入地谈这事
but the more we talked about it...
就越起劲
The more excited we got.
所以没错  我们要同居了
So, yeah, we are.
你们对此有何意见吗
You have anything to say about that?
-为你们俩高兴  -恭喜了
- So happy for you. - Congratulations.
谢谢你们
Thank you.
谢了
你俩明白这就意味着
You two realize this means
我的公寓真的要出租了  对吧
my apartment really is up for grabs, right?
我一定能找到其他住所的
I'm sure I'll find something else.
我也是
Me, too.
这就是我们和昆茵相识的经过
And that's the story of how we met Quinn.
周五  我和罗宾碰面详谈"炒鱿鱼专点"的事
That Friday, I met Robin to see how it went at "fire o'clock."
他们调我去主持直播达人秀
They promoted me to on-air talent.
我将成为桑迪·里维斯的新主持搭档
I'm gonna be Sandy Rivers' new co-host.
我的天
Oh, my God!
怎么会这样
How'd that happen?
还记得跨年夜吗
Remember New Year's Eve?
我临时代替桑迪主持  结果
When I filled in for Sandy, it turns out
环球新闻的执行总裁很喜欢我
the C.E.O. of World Wide News liked me.
他说我挺"带种"的
He said I have "moxie."
他是四十年代的黑帮分子吗
So he's a 1940s gangster?
显然是的
Apparently.
我的薪水涨了不少
And I got a big raise,
所以我决定租下中央公园西区的公寓
so I'm taking this apartment on Central Park West,
这就意味着
which means...
昆茵的公寓
Quinn's apartment.
我已经告诉她那房子归你了
I already told her you'd take it.
多谢了
Wow. Thanks.
没事
Yeah.
也祝贺你
Hey, and congrats.
你真的是名至实归
You deserve it all.
我一直在考虑那件事
You know, I've been thinking about it, and...
我可以跟你重新做回朋友
I can do normal.
为重新做回朋友干杯
To back to normal.
-我该走了  -行
- Uh... I-I should get going. - Yeah.
-你还有好多事要办呢  -没错
- You've got a lot to do. - Totally.
那就  回头见吧
So... Um, see you soon.
回头见
See you soon.
好
Yeah.
后来我们很长一段时间没有见面
We wouldn't see each other for a long time.
不过这事以后再说
But I'll get to that.
听着
Listen, um...
关于我在十年级时和珍娜·克里斯托莉
about me getting to second base in tenth grade
进行到二垒的事
with Jenna Cristalli...
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
我早就把那小贱货给忘了
I've already forgotten about that dumb hobag.
那事不是在我俩看《彼得潘》时发生的
Yeah, um, it didn't happen while we were watching Peter Pan.
而是在我扮演彼得潘时发生的
It happened while I was playing Peter Pan.
这里有我演出时的照片
Here's a photo from the day I was cast.
中间那娃就是我
That's me in the middle.
当时我正值生长迅猛期
But then I had my growth spurt.
演出当晚  我已经长到套不进悬空安全带了
By opening night, I was too big for the flying harness,
于是乎
and, well...
我摔在珍娜·克里斯托莉身上  双手先着胸
I fell hands-first right onto Jenna Cristalli.
她在胸罩里塞的那堆纸巾让我免于双腕骨折
The tissues in her bra saved me two broken wrists.
抱歉  我只是想要有件
I'm sorry. I just, I just wanted
主角不是你的劲爆性事
to have one cool sex story that wasn't you.
好吧  下次你就说
Okay. Next time you tell it,
你偷开了你爸的车
you were in your dad's car,
带她去看金属乐队的演唱会
which you stole to go to a Metallica concert,
然后你和那浪货成功冲上三垒
and you got to third base with that slut.
三垒  指爱抚触摸私密部位
我曾经和某个妞有过一腿
I was once with this chick...
她是世上最棒的老婆
who is just the best wife ever.
谢谢你不介意我的工作
Thank you for being so cool about what I do.
好多男人对这事不是纠结就是嫉妒
A lot of guys would be weird or jealous.
开什么玩笑
Are you kidding?
我有什么资格来说别人  我自己就坏透了
Who am I to judge anyone? I'm the devil!
当然如果你不想跳了  我肯定举双手赞成
I mean, if you ever wanted to stop stripping, I'd support it.
前提是你不想
If you wanted... to.
所以你还是嫉妒咯
So, you are jealous?
什么  才不是  真没有
What? No, no, not at all.
我只是说  有天你不想宽衣解带了
I'm just saying, if you ever wanted to hang up the old G-string,
我完全理解你的决定
I'd completely understand.
不要  我喜欢为钱宽衣解带
Nah, I like taking my clothes off for money.
很好
Great.
听我  听我把话说完
Let me... let me finish.
假设说  什么才能让你不跳呢
Hypothetically, what would make you stop?
假如说...
Hypothetically...
哪天我结婚了  我就不跳脱衣舞了
I would stop stripping if I ever got married.
晚安
Good night.
于是我们决定"重新做回朋友"
And then we agreed to "go back to normal."
可我开始怀疑我们是否能够只做朋友
But I'm starting to wonder if we can ever really just be friends.
总之  这就是我和罗宾从05年起纠结至今的故事
Anyway, that's the story of me and Robin, 2005 to the present.
你们怎么看
What do you think?
我觉得你这故事比一匹布还长
I think your stories are way too long.
我真替他未来的小孩难过
I feel bad for his future kids, dude.
我的孩子肯定爱听我的故事
Hey, my kids are gonna love my stories.
他们肯定爱死这些故事了
They're gonna... yeah, they're gonna love my stories.